[
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "n4f3qsqpzzqh",
        "question": "InternetBound is Imyt's simp.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "ljlq4yo7sowj",
        "question": "Imyt should get a free sippy blast.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "Eddie", "gaR", "Imyt", "InternetBound", "smCharles", "stashiocat" ],
        "id": "innb6nrtudrx",
        "question": "Who amongst the following people is a bully?",
        "responses": [ "Eddie", "gaR", "Imyt", "InternetBound", "smCharles", "stashiocat" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "ftdpl5ja3kst",
        "question": "A fork is the best utensil for sushi.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "with ketchup and a coke" ],
        "id": "xazoikjjveqe",
        "question": "What is the proper way to eat a steak?",
        "responses": [ "with mayo", "well done", "fully cooked", "with ketchup and a coke", "steak is for the birds" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "j0qwz2ji91tl",
        "question": "Imyt was once a hot tub streamer.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "Stashio" ],
        "id": "fphmdhkp0z1s",
        "question": "What is the name of stashiocat's pet cat?",
        "responses": [ "Mandoo", "Stashio", "Garfield", "Mozart", "Sassy", "Pepita" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "Mandoo" ],
        "id": "qsvup6nmb2or",
        "question": "What is the name of Eddie's pet dog?",
        "responses": [ "Mandoo", "Stashio", "Air Bud", "Beethoven", "Chance", "Comet" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "falling into vileplumes" ],
        "id": "a7l7hasy6qht",
        "question": "What is Nevdi most known for?",
        "responses": [ "falling into vileplumes", "perfect draygon fights", "good super rng", "bad phantoon patterns", "world's first PRKD 41" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "izzy" ],
        "id": "cbgkj9utd2wp",
        "question": "Who is known for cooking hotdogs better than just about everyone?",
        "responses": [ "izzy", "Imyt", "Gordon Ramsay", "Guy Fieri", "Emeril Lagasse" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "an entire suburb" ],
        "id": "ldduw4dgoewd",
        "question": "What could a single chimpanzee take out?",
        "responses": [ "an entire suburb", "not even a cat", "an anaconda", "a hippo", "a grizzly bear" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true, false ],
        "id": "2jhqepcgegfa",
        "question": "A single human can fight a grizzly bear with a reasonable chance of winning.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "fixlbcgnpk2c",
        "question": "The bidet is the optimal human-interface device.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "fengbrjccaof",
        "question": "In an average year, Imyt goes on at least 1 vacation each month.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "qwibvlyrljey",
        "question": "With an expensive meal, nothing beats an ice-cold Coca-Cola.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "D2r2kFuMNpKh",
        "question": "InternetBound once defeated a horse by placing a saddle on its back.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "staying on the ground" ],
        "id": "qXlcAFddsYOr",
        "question": "In NEStroid, what is the optimal way for a flying enemy to attack you?",
        "responses": [ "diving from above", "flanking from the rear", "staying on the ground" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "ffXOxJwV8MNU",
        "question": "Imyt once hit Charles in the face during an intense game of Family Feud.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "FRAMES", "GRIMES" ],
        "id": "7PrJqhNLrOE0",
        "question": "Complete the following phrase: PICTURE ______",
        "responses": [ "FRAMES", "GRIMES" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "RvM8MrUE7yCj",
        "question": "Stashiocat once tried to break CynanBot after Charles explicitly said not to.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ true ],
        "id": "XF0JuQOyEh2a",
        "question": "The most popular speedrun category for the SNES game Lethal Weapon is Shark dupe%.",
        "type": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "correctAnswers": [ "2019", "Stashiocat never stopped bullying" ],
        "id": "jN8Pac73Mlaq",
        "question": "What year did stashiocat retire from bullying?",
        "responses": [ "2017", "2019", "2020", "Stashiocat never stopped bullying" ],
        "type": "multiple"
    }
]
